<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<odoo>

    <template id="cooperator_membership_declaration_document">
        <t t-call="web.external_layout">
            <div class="page">
                <!-- Declaration of participation in the cooperative -->
                <h2>
                    <span t-field="o.company_id"/>
                </h2>
                <h3>
                    Declaration of participation in the cooperative
                </h3>
                <p><span t-field="o.lastname"/>,
                    <span t-field="o.firstname"/>
                </p>
                <p>Name, first name / or company represented by: Name, first name</p>

                <p>
                    <span t-field="o.address"/>
                </p>
                <p>Address</p>

                <p><span t-field="o.zip_code"/>,
                    <span t-field="o.city"/>
                </p>
                <p>Postcode, city</p>

                <p>
                    <span t-field="o.birthdate"/>
                </p>
                <p>Born on the</p>

                <p>
                    <span t-field="o.email"/>
                </p>
                <p>e-mail</p>

                <p>
                    <strong>Please tick and fill in: Note: Each member must have at least five business shares at
                        <span t-field="o.share_unit_price"/>
                        €, so no less than 180 € in total in the cooperative. A maximum of 50 cooperative shares are
                        possible (see Section 13, Paragraph 1 of the Articles of Association)
                    </strong>
                </p>

                <p>
                    <!-- TODO: to improve-->
                    <input type="checkbox"
                           t-att-checked="'checked' if o.share_short_name == 'Genossenschaftsanteil' else None"/>
                    I hereby apply for admission to the<span t-field="o.company_id"/>. I would like to participate in
                    the registered cooperative with a total of 5 shares. I undertake to make the payments of 36 €
                    per share in the cooperative as stipulated by the statutes and by law. In total, I therefore
                    undertake to pay 180 €.
                    The articles of association of
                    <span t-field="o.company_id"/>
                    are available on the Internet at
                    <span t-field="o.company_id.website"/>
                    . This will also be handed over on request.
                </p>

                <p>
                    <strong>I acknowledge that the articles of association stipulate a notice period of two years for
                        the end of the financial year
                    </strong>
                </p>

                <p>
                    <!-- TODO: to improve-->
                    <input type="checkbox"
                           t-att-checked="checked"/>
                    I would like to participate in the registered cooperative with
                    <span t-field="o.ordered_parts"/>
                    further shares. I undertake to make the payments of €
                    <span t-field="o.share_unit_price"/>
                    per share in the cooperative, as stipulated by the statutes and by law. In total, I therefore
                    undertake to pay €
                    <span t-esc="o.share_unit_price * o.ordered_parts"/>
                </p>

                <p>
                    <!-- TODO: to improve-->
                    <input type="checkbox"
                           t-att-checked="checked"/>
                    I apply to the board of directors of the cooperative for the option under the articles of
                    association (Section 13 (2)) to allow payment in installments for the payment of the shares.
                    <strong>Note:
                        In this case, we will contact you to agree on the exact terms of the installment payment.
                    </strong>
                </p>

                <p>
                    <!-- TODO: to improve-->
                    <input type="checkbox"
                           t-att-checked="checked"/>
                    I hereby apply for admission to the
                    <span t-field="o.company_id"/>
                    . For social reasons, I would
                    like to participate in the registered cooperative with 1 share. I undertake to make the payments of
                    €
                    <span t-field="o.share_unit_price"/>
                    per share in
                    the cooperative, as stipulated by the statutes and by law. The articles of association of
                    <span t-field="o.company_id"/>
                    can be found on the Internet at
                    <span t-field="o.company_id.website"/>
                    . This will also be handed
                    over on request. <strong>Note: In this case, we will contact you to clarify the conditions for the
                    social
                    tariff.
                </strong> I acknowledge that the articles of association stipulate a notice period of two years for
                    the end of the financial year. After approval you will receive an email from us asking you to
                    transfer your shares to the following account:
                </p>

                <p>
                    <span t-field="o.company_id"/>
                    - IBAN: - BIC:
                </p>
                <p>
                    <strong>Purpose: membership, surname and first name</strong>
                </p>

                <br/>
                <p>
                    <strong>Data protection</strong>
                </p>
                <p>
                    Responsible for data processing is: FoodHub München Market eG, Munich.
                    Data protection officer: Quentin Orain
                    The name and address are required for the membership list of the cooperative (Art. 6 Para. 1c GDPR
                </p>
                <p style="page-break-after:always"></p>

                <!-- General Conditions -->
                <h2>
                    <span t-field="o.company_id"/>
                </h2>
                <p>
                    In conjunction with Section 30 (1) Sentence 1 No. 1 GEnG). The tax identification number and the
                    date of birth are required in order to be able to pay the withholding tax in the event of a profit
                    distribution. (Art. 6 Paragraph 1c GDPR in conjunction with Section 45 d Paragraph 1 EStG) and to be
                    able to carry out the legally required queries on the church tax attribute. (Art. 6 Paragraph 1c in
                    conjunction with Section 51a Paragraph 2c, 2e EStG). You will be invited to meetings by the
                    cooperative via the address, if applicable the e-mail address (Art. 6 Paragraph 1c GDPR) in
                    conjunction with Section 46 Paragraph 1 Sentence 1 GenG in conjunction with Section 6 No. 4 GenG),
                    beyond that Informed about offers of the cooperative within the framework of membership (Art. 6
                    Paragraph 1b GDPR) in conjunction with Section 1 Paragraph 1 in conjunction with the Articles of
                    Association. The cooperative has a legitimate interest in uncomplicated and legally secure
                    fulfillment of its obligations. The provision of personal data is required by law or by the articles
                    of association. Failure to provide it would mean that membership cannot be established. The personal
                    data will not be passed on to third parties unless consent has been given in individual cases.
                    However, we are legally obliged to allow access to personal data in some cases. This affects, for
                    example, other members, the statutory auditing association and authorities, especially the tax
                    office. The data is stored in different ways. All tax-relevant information is kept for ten years
                    (§147 AO). The data in the list of members (name and address in accordance with Section 30,
                    Paragraph 2, Clause 1, No. 3 GenG) will not be deleted even after leaving. (Section 30, Paragraph 2,
                    Clause 1, No. 3 GenG). You have the right to information from the person responsible about the
                    relevant personal data as well as to correction or deletion or restriction of processing (unless
                    this is contrary to a legal regulation). A data transfer can also be requested if the signatory
                    wishes his data to be transferred to a third party.
                </p>
                <p>In addition, you have the right to lodge a complaint with the supervisory authority (state
                    commissioner for data protection).
                </p>
                <br/>
                <p>Place, date:</p>
                <p>Signature member:</p>
                <br/>
                <p>Approval by the cooperative: The application is granted:</p>
                <br/>
                <p>Place, date:</p>
                <p>Signature of the board of directors:</p>
                <p style="page-break-after:always"></p>

                <!-- Declaration of membership -->
                <h2>Declaration of membership</h2>

                <p>I hereby declare that I am a member of the association</p>
                <p><strong><span t-field="o.company_id"/></strong> with effect from <span t-field="o.date"/></p>
                <p>Surname: <span t-field="o.lastname"/></p>
                <p>First name: <span t-field="o.firstname"/></p>
                <p>Address: <span t-field="o.address"/></p>
                <p>Postcode / City: <span t-field="o.zip_code"/> <span t-field="o.city"/></p>
                <p>E-mail: <span t-field="o.email"/></p>
                <p>Phone number: <span t-field="o.phone"/></p>

                <p>
                    By providing my email address, I agree to receive communications from the association by email. The
                    email address will never be passed on to third parties. I can revoke this declaration at any time.
                    The dispatch of information relevant to the association (e.g. invitation to the general meeting)
                    cannot be ruled out with the opt-out decision.
                </p>

                <p>I have taken note of the statutes.</p>
                <p>I pay <strong>10 euros</strong> as an annual fee</p>
                <p>
                    The annual fee for the current year is due and payable immediately in full. I will transfer the
                    contribution to the club account at
                    <strong> GLS Bank - IBAN DE60 430 609 671 075 937 900 - BIC GENODEM1GLS.
                    </strong>
                </p>

                <p>
                    In the following years it is due and payable on January 15th. I will pay this contribution annually
                    to the above-mentioned association account. Membership is automatically extended by 1 year if it is
                    not canceled 6 weeks before the end of the year.
                </p>
                <br/>

                <p>Place, date:</p>
                <p>Signature:</p>

                <!-- TODO: t-field -->
                <p>
                    Foodhub e. V. Munich, c / o Impact HUB, Gotzinger Straße 8, 81371 Munich VR 208582 District Court
                    Munich Bank details: GLS Community Bank eGIBAN DE60 430 609 671 075 937 900 - BIC GENODEM1GL
                </p>

                <p><strong>Please send at:</strong></p>
                <!-- TODO: t-field -->
                <p>Foodhub e. V. Munich Kristin Mansmann c / o Impact HUB - Gotzinger Strasse 8, 81371 Munich</p>
            </div>
        </t>

    </template>

    <template id="cooperator_membership_declaration">
        <t t-call="web.html_container">
            <t t-foreach="docs" t-as="o">
                <t t-call="foodhub_munich_custom.cooperator_membership_declaration_document"
                   t-lang="o.partner_id.lang"/>
            </t>
        </t>
    </template>

</odoo>
